Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - Second Alpha Sequence A-Z
        - Nightmares On Wax - Smokers delight (disc two), 1995; SR-28494; Nightmares On Wax (Box 92)
          Catalog # WARP LP 36; A-side Matrix # WARPLP-36-C1
        - Nubian Crackers - Cracker beats vol. II, 1993; SR-28495; Nubian Crackers (Box 92)
          Catalog # 71219; A-side Matrix # 71219-PHATT
        - Nubian Crackers - Cracker beats vol. III, 1993; SR-28496; Nubian Crackers (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-28497. Different discs.
          Catalog # 71220; A-side Matrix # 71220-1 A
        - Nubian Crackers - Cracker beats vol. II, 1993; SR-28497; Nubian Crackers (Box 92)
          In same jacket as # SR-28496. Different discs. Label obscured
        - Nubian Crackers - Cracker beats vol. IV, 1994; SR-28498; Nubian Crackers (Box 92)
          Catalog # 71223; A-side Matrix # 71223-PHAT 1-1 F/W MT
        - Nubian Crackers - Cracker beats vol. VII, 1995; SR-28499; Nubian Crackers (Box 92)
          Catalog # 71231; A-side Matrix # 71231 PHAT MJS
        - Pan Assembly - Pan calypso, 1986; SR-29476; Pan Assembly (Box 92)
          Catalog # HVLP 002; A-side Matrix # CAROTTE-01186-A1
          Hot Vinyl
          Trinidad & Tobago
        - Pan Vibes Steel Orchestra - Trinidad Carnival steel band, 1983; SR-29477; Pan Vibes Steel Orchestra (Box 92)
          Catalog # ELP 001; A-side Matrix # TUCAS-119 A -1-
          Ebony Records
        - Plump DJs - In stereo; Squeaks & bleeps, 2003; SR-29478; Plump DJs (Box 92)
          Catalog # FLR38X; A-side Matrix # FLR 038 C
        - Ross, Diana - It's my house; No one gets the prize; The boss, 1979; SR-28834; Ross, Diana (Box 92)
          Catalog # PR-54; A-side Matrix # PR-54-A-65606-D-18B
          Motown
        - Shadow - Constant jamming, 1976; SR-30929; Shadow (Box 92)
          Catalog # CR-003; A-side Matrix # CR003 A
        - Sly & The Family Stone - Dance to the music, 1991; SR-28835; Sly & The Family Stone (Box 92)
          Catalog # THBL 1.029; A-side Matrix # THBL-1029A
          Thunderbolt
          Middlesex, England
        - Beckett - Vincy mas, 1983; SR-30881; Beckett (Box 146)
          Catalog # COCOA 0005; A-side Matrix # PV 0005 A-2
          Cocoa Records
        - Blackwell Project - Explicit lyrics, 1985; SR-30882; Blackwell Project (Box 146)
          Catalog # EMDS 6558; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6558-A
          Emergency Records
        - Blue Magic - Blue Magic, 1974; SR-30883; Blue Magic (Box 146)
          Catalog # SD 7038; A-side Matrix # ST-C-733001-BB-PE
          ATCO Records
        - Carr, Jerry - This must be heaven, 1981; SR-30884; Carr, Jerry (Box 146)
          Catalog # CR 19330; A-side Matrix # ST-CR-814823-B
          Cherie
        - D Original - How a DJ works, 2001; SR-8122; D Original (Box 146)
          Catalog # EBM#02; A-side Matrix # EBM 02-A
          Eastern Breakz Movement
          Sebring, Florida
        - D Train - Music, 1983; SR-8123; D Train; "D" Train (Box 146)
          Catalog # PRL 14109 AS; A-side Matrix # PRL-14109-A
          Prelude Records
        - dáKrash - dáKrash, 1988; SR-8125; dáKrash; Dá Krash (Box 146)
          Catalog # C1-48355; A-side Matrix # C-1-48355-DMM-21
        - dáKrash - dáKrash, 1988; SR-8126; dáKrash; Dá Krash (Box 146)
        - Daft Punk - Homework (disc one), 1996; SR-8136; Daft Punk (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8137. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 42610 16; A-side Matrix # A1 426101
          Virgin
        - Daft Punk - Homework (disc two), 1996; SR-8137; Daft Punk (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8136. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8 42610 15; A-side Matrix # C1 426111
        - Daft Punk - Discovery (disc one), 2008; SR-8138; Daft Punk (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8139. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8496061 2; A-side Matrix # 07243-8496071-1 A2
        - Daft Punk - Discovery (disc two), 2008; SR-8139; Daft Punk (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8138. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 8496061 2; A-side Matrix # 07243-8496081-0 A2
        - Dakouri, Tina - Inokeka - Nokeka, 1983; SR-8124; Dakouri, Tina (Box 146)
          Catalog # SK 84001; A-side Matrix # SK 84001 A2 I
          ESKA Production
        - Dalton & Dubarri - Choice, 1979; SR-8127; Dalton & Dubarri (Box 146)
          Catalog # HT 19226; A-side Matrix # STHT-794219-A
          Hilltak Records
        - Dance - In lust, 1981; SR-8128; Dance (Box 146)
          Catalog # STAT LP3 A; A-side Matrix # STAT LP3 A1
          Statik Records
        - Dance - Soul force, 1982; SR-8129; Dance (Box 146)
          Catalog # STAT LP 12; A-side Matrix # STAT LP 12 A1
        - Danmass - The woman I love, 1998; SR-8140; Danmass (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8141. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPEC 114; A-side Matrix # SPEC-114-A2
          Dust 2 Dust Records
          London, United Kingdom
        - Incredible Melting Man - Funky plaid coat EP, 1998; SR-8141; Incredible Melting Man (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-8140. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPEC 124; A-side Matrix # SPEC 124-A1
        - Direct Drive - Don't depend on me, 1982; SR-8200; Direct Drive (Box 146)
          Catalog # DRIVE 20/20; A-side Matrix # DRIVE 20/20 AB PAG
          Oval
        - Duran Duran - Rio, 1982; SR-30885; Duran Duran (Box 146)
          Catalog # ST-12211; A-side Matrix # ST 1-12211 2 5
          Harvest
        - Duran Duran - Planet earth (night version), 1981; SR-30886; Duran Duran (Box 146)
          Catalog # 12 EMI 5137; A-side Matrix # 12 EMI 5137 A-2
          EMI
        - Empress - Empress, 1982; SR-30887; Empress (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30888. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRL 14102 AS; A-side Matrix # PRL-14102-A
        - Empress - Take a risk, 1982; SR-30888; Empress (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30887. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRL D 545; A-side Matrix # PRLD-545-AS
        - Fad Gadget - Under the flag, 1982; SR-30889; Fad Gadget (Box 146)
          Catalog # STUMM 8; A-side Matrix # STUMM 8 A
          Mute
        - Foreigner - 4, 1981; SR-30890; Foreigner (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30891
          Catalog # SD 16999; A-side Matrix # STA-814727-A SP 0-6SM 1-1
        - Foreigner - 4, 1981; SR-30891; Foreigner (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30890
          Catalog # SD 16999; A-side Matrix # STA-814727-D
        - Girls Can't Help It - Pure wild, 1983; SR-30892; Girls Can't Help It (Box 146)
          Catalog # 1-23966; A-side Matrix # 1-23966-A-SH1 O B-18489
        - Grant, Eddy - Walking on sunshine, 1979; SR-30893; Grant, Eddy (Box 146)
          Catalog # ICELP 5001; A-side Matrix # ICELP 5001 A-11-1-2
          Ice
        - Human League - Dare, 1981; SR-30894; Human League (Box 146)
          Catalog # SP-6-4892; A-side Matrix # SPO-6-4892-A-TH1
          A&M Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Imagination - Body talk, 1981; SR-30895; Imagination (Box 146)
          Catalog # MCA-5271; A-side Matrix # MCA-2765-W2 MCA8G
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Indeep - Last night a DJ saved my life, 1983; SR-30896; Indeep (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30897. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SNY 1201; A-side Matrix # SNY-1201-A
          Sound of New York
        - Indeep - Last night a DJ saved my life, 1983; SR-30897; Indeep (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30896. Multiple copies.
        - Kano - New York cake, 1981; SR-30898; Kano (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30899. Different discs.
          Catalog # WTG 19327; A-side Matrix # ST-WTG 814813-A- 0-15143-2
          Mirage
        - Kano - Can't hold back (your loving), 1981; SR-30899; Kano (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30898. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 299; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40473-2
        - Mighty Bottle of Antigua - Calypsoes by the Mighty Bottle of Antigua, 1975; SR-30900; Mighty Bottle of Antigua; Mighty Bottle (Box 146)
          Catalog # 9025; A-side Matrix # 9025A
          Camille Records
        - Nena - 99 luftballoons, 1983; SR-30901; Nena (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30902. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # CBS A 12.3060; A-side Matrix # 11-3060-1A-1
          CBS
        - Nena - 99 luftballoons, 1983; SR-30902; Nena (Box 146)
          In same jacket as # SR-30901. Multiple copies.
        - Numan, Gary - Metal rhythm, 1988; SR-30903; Numan, Gary (Box 146)
          Catalog # EIRSA 1021; A-side Matrix # EIRSA 1021 A-1J-1-1
          I.R.S. Records
        - Numan, Gary - The skin mechanic, 1989; SR-30904; Numan, Gary (Box 94)
          Catalog # EIRSA 1019; A-side Matrix # EIRSA 1019 A-1U-1-3
        - Quando Quango - Love tempo, SR-30905; Quando Quango (Box 94)
          Catalog # OFNY-5; A-side Matrix # OFNY-5-A
          Of Factory New York
          Belgium
        - Quando Quango - Love tempo, 1983; SR-30906; Quando Quango (Box 94)
          Catalog # FBN 23; A-side Matrix # FBN 23A
          Factory Benelux
        - Rhythm Within - Don't keep me waiting, 1992; SR-30907; Rhythm Within (Box 94)
          Catalog # PEAK 122; A-side Matrix # PEAK 122 A-1
          Tone Records
        - Robe - Turn on the moon, 1987; SR-30908; Robe (Box 94)
          Catalog # 2000AD-ST4; A-side Matrix # 2000AD-ST-4-A S-18074 RE1
          2000 AD Records
        - Rochelle - My magic man, 1985; SR-30909; Rochelle (Box 94)
          Catalog # 0-20376; A-side Matrix # O-20376-A-SH1 OB-21842-SH1 SLM 10557
        - Rodway - Don't knock it 'til you try it, 1983; SR-30910; Rodway; Rodway, Steve (Box 94)
          Catalog # JD-13119; A-side Matrix # JD-1349-A-10
          Millenium
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Real eyes, 1980; SR-30911; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 94)
          Catalog # AL 9540; A-side Matrix # AL 9540-SA-1A
        - Silver, Platinum And Gold - Hollywood, 1981; SR-30912; Silver, Platinum And Gold (Box 94)
          Catalog # JMH-77101; A-side Matrix # JMH-77101 47846-A HR-10012A
          Neptune Records
        - Specimen - Returning (from a journey), 1983; SR-30913; Specimen (Box 94)
          Catalog # LONX 24; A-side Matrix # LONX 24 A 3 420
        - Summer, Donna - She works hard for the money, 1983; SR-30914; Summer, Donna (Box 94)
          In same jacket as # SR-30915. Different discs.
          Catalog # 422-812 265-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422-812-265-1-AS-RE-HRMI
          Mercury
        - Summer, Donna - She works hard for the money, 1983; SR-30915; Summer, Donna (Box 94)
          In same jacket as # SR-30914. Different discs.
          Catalog # MK 249; A-side Matrix # MK-249-2-57456-PRC-C-1-1-1-A
        - Tenants - The Tenants, 1983; SR-30916; Tenants (Box 94)
          Catalog # BFE 38671; A-side Matrix # AS 38671-1C
          Epic
        - To Kalon - Coming to get you, 1981; SR-30917; To Kalon (Box 94)
          Catalog # BUBLY 701; A-side Matrix # BUBLY-701 A1
          E.D.M. Champagne
        - Winter, Edgar - Standing on rock, 1981; SR-30918; Winter, Edgar (Box 94)
          Catalog # JZ 36494; A-side Matrix # AL-36494
          Blue Sky
        - Wiseguys - Executive suite (disc one), 1996; SR-30919; Wiseguys (Box 94)
          Catalog # WALLLP 008; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 008-A
        - Wiseguys - Executive suite (disc two), 1996; SR-30920; Wiseguys (Box 94)
          Catalog # WALLLP 008; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 008-C
        - Yankovic, Weird Al - In 3-D, 1984; SR-30921; Yankovic, Weird Al; Yankovic, Al (Box 94)
          Catalog # FZ 39221; A-side Matrix # AL 39221-2B
          Rock 'n' Roll Records
        - Yellowman - Strikes again, 1989; SR-30922; Yellowman (Box 94)
          Catalog # VPRL-1078; A-side Matrix # VPRL-1078-A YELLOWMAN
          Mixing Lab
          Jamaica, New York
        - Yellowman & Fathead - One Yellowman, 1982; SR-30923; Yellowman & Fathead; Yellowman (Box 94)
          Catalog # JJ-067; A-side Matrix # LP-JJ-067-A
          Hit Bound
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Let's find a way - Youngblood, Bobby, 1984; SR-30924; Let's find a way (Box 94)
          Catalog # YG-001; A-side Matrix # YG 001 A-R
          Young Guys Records
          Bronx, New York
        - 9th Creation - Superheroes, 1979; SR-30925; 9th Creation (Box 94)
          Catalog # HT 1101; A-side Matrix # HT-1101-AS
        - Various - Survival...Mind & Matter; Megamix, 1983; SR-30926 (Box 94)
          Catalog # SUR LP 002; A-side Matrix # SURLP 002 A
          Survival Records
        - Various - Total recall-Volcano 2, 1992; SR-30927 (Box 94)
          Catalog # VP 1190; A-side Matrix # VPRL-1190-A TOTAL RECALL # VP-CM
          VP Records